<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<messages>
  <message day="2014-11-19">Never give up on something you can't go a day without thinking about.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-20">The hardest part of acting like you dont care, is knowing how much you actually do.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-21">The worst feeling is when something is killing you inside, and you have to act like you don't care.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-23">Sometimes you have to forget what you feel and remember what you deserve.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-24">Relationships end because once the person has you, they stop doing the things it took to get you.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-25">The worst feeling ever is not knowing whether you should wait or give up..</message>
  <message day="2014-11-26">There comes a point in your life when you realize who really matters, who never did, and who always will.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-27">The couples that are meant to be, are the ones who go through everything that is meant to tear them apart, and come out even stronger.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-28">Don't stress over anything that you can't change.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-29">Over thinking is what really kills you.</message>
  <message day="2014-11-30">It's sad when you realize you aren't as important to someone as you thought you were.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-09">If you give up, it means you never really wanted it.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-01">Treat your girl right, or sit back and watch someone else do it for you.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-02">Be with someone who won't stay mad at you, who can't stand not talking to you, and who's afraid of losing you.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-03">If a girl is stupid enough to love you after you broke her heart, I guarantee you, she is the one.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-04">Fake friends believe in rumors. Real friends believe in you.	</message>
  <message day="2014-12-05">Don't change for anyone. People will love you for who you are, or you don't need them in your life.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-06">Everybody deserves second chances, but not for the same mistakes.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-07">Don't lie, don't cheat, and don't make promises you can't keep.</message>
  <message day="2014-12-08">Don't apologize, and then do it again.</message>
  <message day="2015-08-03">testing</message>
</messages>